A 90-day mission becomes a 15-year journey of opportunity.
Good Night Oppy is a documentary film directed by Ryan White.
The inspirational true story of Opportunity, a rover that was sent to Mars
for a 90-day mission but ended up surviving for 15 years.
Follow Opportunity’s groundbreaking journey on Mars and the remarkable bond
forged between a robot and her humans millions of miles away.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Angela Bassett.
Self, played by Steve Squyres.
Self, played by Jennifer Trosper.
Self, played by Rob Manning.
Self, played by Kobie Boykins.
Self, played by Ashitey Trebi-Ollennu.
Good Night Oppy is a 2022 American documentary film directed
by Ryan White and narrated by Angela Bassett.
It had its world premiere at the 49th Telluride
Film Festival on September 3, 2022.
It was released in a limited release on November 4, 2022, by Amazon
Studios, prior to streaming on Prime Video on November 23, 2022.
The film explores themes of planet mars, nasa, space exploration.